Greater Buffalo Industrial Union Council Records 5254
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Anti-discrimination (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Federal Communications Commission (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Education (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Economic Cooperation Administration (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Cost of Living - Publications (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Full Employment (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Civil Rights (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Housing, 1943-1949 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Capehart, Homer E. - U.S. Senator (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Atomic Energy (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Anti-labor Legislation, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Anti-labor Legislation, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Anti-labor Legislation, 1948-1959 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Anti-labor Legislation, 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Cost of Living (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Mead, James M. - U.S. Senator (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Price Control (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Pillion, John R. - U.S. Congressman (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Poll Tax, 1945-1948 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Poll Tax, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Office for Emergency Management (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Gorski, Chester C. - U.S. Congressman (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Minimum Wage (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Radwan, Edmund P. - U.S. Congressman (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Labor Extension Service Bill (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Jehle, Edward P. - U.S. Congressman (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Javits, Jacob K. - U.S. Senator (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Ives, Irving M. - U.S. Senator (Box 6, Folder 20)
- International Affairs (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Housing, 1954-1959 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Missouri Valley Authority (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Taxes (Box 7, Folder 10)
- City Planning (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Catholic Church (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Buffalo Evening News (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Buffalo Courier Express - Elwood (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Buffalo Council of Social Agencies (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Buffalo Council of Churches (Box 7, Folder 15)
- American Cancer Society (Box 7, Folder 14)
- U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Rent Control, 1946-1949 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Tobin, Maurice J. - Secretary of Labor (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Community Service Committee, 1950-1958 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Tauriello, Anthony F, - U.S. Congressman (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Surplus Food, 1953-1957 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- St. Lawrence Seaway & Power Project, 1953-1957 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- St. Lawrence Seaway & Power Project, 1949-1952 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- St. Lawrence Seaway & Power Project, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- St. Lawrence Seaway & Power Project, 1940-1944 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Social Security (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Rent Control, 1951-1957 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Universal Military Training, 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Win the Peace Rally, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Y.W.CA (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Y.M.C.A. (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Victory Clothing Collection Drive (Box 7, Folder 39)
- U.S.O (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Speeches - Miller (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Sister Elizabeth Kenny Foundation (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Red Cross (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Civic Full Employment Committee (City of Buffalo) (Box 7, Folder 21)
- National Planning Association (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Community Service Committee, 1945-1949 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- March of Dimes (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Labor Committee to Combat Intolerance (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Labor and Religion (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Juvenile Delinquency (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Goodwill Industries (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Junior Achievement (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Community Service Committee - Union Counseling (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Community Service Committee - Program (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Greater Buffalo Industrial Union Council AFL-CIO Audit Report, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  Dec. 22nd
- Publicity - Radio (Box 7, Folder 34)